musictri.be 2019-06-01

# Privacy Policy - Music Tribe

We respect the privacy of every individual who visits our site and take the confidentiality of your personal information very seriously.

This Privacy Policy explains how we gather and use information.

  1. ##### What is Personal Information?

Personal information is data that refers directly or indirectly to a person this includes but is not limited to:

    * Name
    * Address
    * Telephone Number
    * Email Address

We will only use such information when we are legally allowed to or when you give us consent.

  2. ##### Your Consent to This Privacy Policy

By accessing, browsing this site or providing us with your personal information, you agree to the terms of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with any of the terms here, please do not access this site or provide your personal information.

This policy may be altered at any time. When this happens, any changes will be reflected on this page.

  3. ##### Collection of Personal Information

We will not collect your personal information unless you provide this to us voluntarily. You may withdraw this authorization at any time by emailing us at [help@musictribe.com](mailto:help@musictribe.com) and we will delete all your personal information on this site. 

If you need more information, please refer to Chapter 3 of the EU-GDPR 2016/679

  4. ##### How we use your information

When we collect your personal information, we will always specify the purpose for collecting.

Any personal information you provide will be used with your permission to forward you brochures, magazines, etc. or to offer you certain products or services you may be interested in.

If you want to stop or limit our contact with you send us a request at [help@musictribe.com](mailto:help@musictribe.com)

  5. ##### Sharing of Your Information

We may share your personal information with the following:

    * Affiliates or contractors who help with our business and are bound to confidentiality
    * Law enforcement, judicial or government authorities for legal proceedings, fraud prevention, investigations into legal activities or as otherwise required by law
    * Other business entities we may plan to merge with
  6. ##### Security

We use technical and organizational security measures to protect your personal data against accidental or unlawful destruction, loss, alteration and unauthorized disclosure or access

  7. ##### Google AdWords

We use Google AdWords Remarketing to advertise Music Tribe across the internet.

You may be shown ads based on what parts of the Music Tribe website you have visited by placing a cookie on your web browser. This cookie does not identify you or give access to your computer or mobile device.

If you do not wish to see ads from Music Tribe, you can:

    1. Opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting [Google’s Ads Settings.](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated)
    2. Opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page. ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)

Most browsers allow you to refuse or delete cookies. Find out how you can do this with your specific browser by clicking on any of the links below.

    1. [https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en (Chrome)](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en)
    2. [ https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences (Firefox)](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences)
    3. [ http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/ (Opera)](http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/)
    4. [ https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies (Internet Explorer)](https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies)
    5. [https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411 (Safari)](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411)
    6. [https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy (Edge)](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy)
  8. ##### Our Details/Imprint

This website is owned and operated by Music Tribe Services PH Corp.

We are registered under registration number: CS201422110

Our registered office and principal place of business is at: 26th Floor, Centuria Medical Makati, Century City Kalayaan Ave., Brgy. Poblacion, Makati City, Philippines 1210

You can email us at [help@musictribe.com](mailto:help@musictribe.com)
